There was a guy back in the day who,
and again, I copied this, standing on the
shoulders of giants.
There's a guy from Northern Ireland,
and he said,
"50 ways in 50 days to improve your
business." So I sign up.
This guy emails me every single day for 50
days telling me how to better my
business. On the 52nd day,
he tells me to buy his book.
I didn't buy his book.
He then adds me to a broadcast. Now,
an automation is an automation.
Broadcast is on top.
And he broadcasts every day,
and they're pretty good emails.
But one day,
he sends me an email drunk from his dad's
funeral, and
you can tell he's drunk from the email.
Then at the end, it says, "PS,
if you think it's inappropriate for me to
sell to
you off my dad's death,
go fuck yourself." It's the best email
I've ever read to
this day,
and I bought his book off the back of
that. So I was inspired from that.
I have a lead magnet for my fitness
business.
Also,
there's another lead magnet squeeze page I
have where if you ever see me do
these videos where I critique people's
social media, when people apply, I chuck
them into the 30-day automation. Now,
the beauty of that is for some reason,
people that apply for a roast,
when we add them to the 30-day funnel, we
get double the attribution of sales. Why?
No idea.
And I think it's quite good as a business
owner to tell you that